Andrés Eduardo Casadiegos Gómez

Systems Engineer

Systems engineer with 2 years of experience in the analysis, development and maintenance of business applications, mainly with .Net C#, Angular and PL/SQL technologies, but always with the willingness to continue learning to grow professionally.

I am a young man passionate about programming, responsible in the assigned tasks, with a competitive spirit and continuous improvement, both personal and professional, looking for opportunities in which to develop all my knowledge.

Work History

2020-08

Intern - Software Development Engineer

- 2020-12

GRUPO EMPRESARIAL CSS SAS, Bucaramanga

Technologies: PHP / Laravel.

Description: Participation in the development of a email advertising

marketing system in its beta version.

2021-05 - present Software development engineer

Norsoft S.AS, Cucúta

Client: Sodexo / Pluxee Colombia

Technologies: .Net Framework, Oracle PL/SQ, .Net 6.0, .Net 5.0, .Net Core

3.1, Angular, SASS, CSS, Javascript, Typescript.

Management Framework: Scrum. Some Projects I worked on:

- BILLING MIGRATION: ERP change that involved developments on Condor, Sodexo's core card system, to consume services in Azure and build stored procedures in charge of migrating customer and affiliate invoices to the new ERP.
- VIRTUAL CARD: Developments on Condor, Sodexo's core card system, and on the PaymentGateway microservice for activation of QR payments, to allow customers to request, load and manage virtual cards that are enrolled in their mobile device, to later be able to make payments via QR.
- MAINTENANCE: Maintenance work on Sodexo core systems such as:
 Front-end bug fixes, rest APIs, microservices and database procedures.
 Changes in the look and feel of the applications, improvements in source code to optimize processes and implement patterns for clean code.
- **NEXOZ PSE PAYMENT**: Front-end and back-end developments to implement payment with PSE in Sodexo's Nexoz application, a platform where clients can request cash dispersions for their beneficiaries.
- NEXOZ DATABASE NORMALIZATION: Normalization of tables in the database of Sodexo's Nexoz application, under the guidelines of the technical leader of the project, to optimize queries and have a more decoupled and organized database model.

Note: These are some of the projects and tasks I have done. In the link to my portfolio you can find the complete list of all the projects I worked on.

Education

2016-01

Systems engineer

- 2020-12

Universidad Autonóma de Bucaramanga, Bucaramanga

Personal Info

Email

acasadiego199827@gmail.com

Phone

+57 3209668783

GitHub

https://github.com/acasadiegos

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/andréseduardo-casadiegos-gómezb579501b8/

Website

https://portafolio-andres-casadiegos-001add792e5d.herokuapp.com

Skills

 HTML

CSS/Sass

Bootstrap

Javascript

Angular

C#

.Net Core

.Net Framework

API Rest, Microservicios, Clean Architecture

Asp .Net Core MVC

Bases de datos Oracle, PL/SQL

Git

Languages

Spanish (Native)



English (B1)

Courses	
2022-01	Building RESTFul Web APIs with ASP.NET Core 6
2021-12	Angular course on Udemy by instructor Fernando Herrera
2023-10	ASP.NET Core Clean Architecture and Domain Driven Design (DDD)
2023-11	Microservices with ASP.NET Core, Docker and RabbitMQ
2022-12	B1 English course at the ENGLISH FOR ALL Institute (Cúcuta).

Schooling - Technical Bachelor Graphic Design

Instituto Técnico Industrial Salesiano, Cúcuta

2004-01

- 2015-12